some is is she all right though? Like
she be giving me like bad batch vibes,
you know what I mean? Like you know what
I mean? Like got a bad batch, you know?
That Chris Tucker [ __ ] that that that
Smokeoky [ __ ]
like you know what I mean? One of them
once like YO CHAT WHAT'S GOING ON?
The one [music]
Amanda Seals I think I don't know if
she's losing it these days. Yeah. I
don't know what really happened to
Amanda Seals. Look like she been I don't
know if she going through it or what,
bro. This week.
Okay.
All right.
>> What's up everybody? I'll be
>> now look like she's beefing with
Charlemagne the God.
I thought a man of seals was like all
them like all the there's a bunch of
like little black chicks that's in that
sphere that's mad woke like
[clears throat] they're kind of usually
part of Charlemagne's posi like when I
mean posi like they [ __ ] with
Charlemagne. Um Shorty look like she is
defecting and I don't know why but I'm
interested in finding out. I don't know
what's going on.
This is her from yesterday.
Do I have insurance on your legs?
>> What the [ __ ]
>> No. Why would I have insurance on my
legs? What was one of my favorite
interviews?
You mean that I was interviewed or I
interviewed people? Me being interviewed
or me interviewing somebody?
Is some Is she all right though? Like
she be giving me like bad batch vibes.
You know what I mean? Like you know what
I mean? Like got a bad batch, you know?
that Chris Tucker [ __ ] that that that
Smokey [ __ ]
like, you know what I mean? One of them
ones like, "Yo, chat, what's going on?"
Um,
these will be for sale when I'm on the
road this week.
>> Nah, this not the same lady. It's not
the same lady, y'all.
No, I did not find a venue in Oakland.
Oakland got mad at me for, you know,
saying the truth, so I said, "Oh, y'all
got it."
Shauna, you're you're not me
people. The gateways, do you feel you
have been validated with your experience
as a human and artist in the industry
of
acknowledgement? same Adisa. The feeling
is mutual in terms of the Democrats, you
know, uh Joe Biden or Joe Mansion and
she
>> like he's read books. However,
>> from what I understand, what you're
saying is like do I feel like I did like
I I went to the industry and I did what
I needed to do.
I mean,
yes and no.
you know, like I I mean I I went to the
industry to
achieve
a certain level of
acknowledgement. Same Ada, the feeling
is mutual.
Um and I do feel like I did that.
However,
I think it was only to a certain extent
because
um
because basically once I
>> Come on.
>> Why would I do a podcast with
Charlamagne?
>> Whoa.
>> Why? Why? Why? Why would I do a podcast?
We had great chemistry until I realized
that he was a ridiculous person and he
was a snake. So then we don't have great
chemistry anymore.
>> Holy. Now,
only reason I'm even like even watching
this is because these people um like I
I've always said I think I think
Charlemagne got a great network and I
think Charlemagne has like helped some
of these like extra pro blackack people
get in positions and when anything has
ever happened like you know like for
example uh um you get that hating ass
[ __ ] Mayo trying to say some [ __ ] about
me you don't see any of my peers they
wouldn't be Like, nah, no. We [ __ ] with
a hold on now. Cuz really I don't have
peers. Like, well, I have peers, but
like I I don't have like a posi that's
in the industry. I really only have my
audience, right?
Charlemagne has like he has a couple of
them, you know what I mean? Um,
there's that black lady. She she be
doing she be she be sounding like a
lawyer. She be sounding like fake smart
type [ __ ] Y'all know who I'm talking
about.
Do you know who I'm talking about
though? Like I I noticed that with
Charlemagne. And by the way, there's
nothing wrong with that. I think
Charmaine created a web of people that
he helped put on that when [ __ ] happens
to him. It's like Jay-Z. You know why
Jay-Z's untouchable?
Nobody is going to stand. Like, you ever
see when we're seeing the loudest [ __ ]
about Jay-Z, nobody want to talk about
it? This always happens, right? like all
of the people or a lot of people that
have been positioned in the media got a
you know a leg up from him or you know
they [ __ ] with him like he made sure he
put people in position and like he has a
posi like you know what I mean people
defend him so it works to his benefit I
think Charlemagne learned that and he um
yeah Angela Ry yeah like Angela Ry like
Charlemagne has like a group as Well,
you know what I mean? And it's mostly
like a bunch of pro black woke
[ __ ] Um, not all of them are
in hip-hop, but you know, they they they
they [ __ ] with him heavy. And, you know,
they also [ __ ] with him because he
brings them into the hip-hop space. He's
used his brand to elevate theirs. And,
you know, it's just just a posi. I
thought she was part of the posi low
key. So, when I'm seeing her say [ __ ]
about Charlemagne, I'm like, yo, did she
get kicked out the whip? Like, what's
happening? Feel me? And I keep telling
you she's doing that smoky [ __ ] I don't
know what's going on. So I just want to
know.
>> He's also not an intellectual like he's
reg.
>> Somebody say I got Flaco.
Here's the thing [snorts] because this
is the important and I'm glad you said
that and shout out to Flaco.
What I'm saying is no. No. Like all the
new media dudes [ __ ] with me. Like Trapo
Rosses, Flock, they they do.
The difference between like what,
how do I say this? The difference
between the people that y'all are
talking about with me, Flockco or
whoever,
Angela Ry will be on CNN
like for for Jay-Z. Jay-Z put a bunch of
people on and then put them in powerful
positions that he had influence at. You
get what I'm saying? Like Flaco would be
a dope um um you could say posi whatever
if
I had the power or authority to put
Flaco on like I don't know the Joe
Button podcast or something, you know
what I mean? Or put him on, I don't
know, put him on some [ __ ] network,
right? That's what I've realized. And I'
I've given Charlemagne a lot of credit
for this. Charlemagne put these [ __ ]
on. Like literally put them on, right?
Like he put them in positions to the
point where they became almost like
they're like a defense squad, but
they're a defense squad on huge
platforms, not just their own, right?
Like like when he found that bum Taxton,
Tax Stone was just a hood [ __ ] trying
to kill people. I mean, ultimately he
did. That's why he's in jail forever.
But um he he found him at a local bodega
and then he put that bum on MTV. Do you
get what I'm saying? Like he's helped
people like that. Like you know, like
Charlemagne has like a unlimited pass up
at MTV. I don't know if still anymore,
but he did. He would put people on that
platform and those people are indebted
to him, right? Like it's even, you know,
there was a time when people thought
that Charlemagne got too PC and, you
know, Schultz is popping off and people
felt like, damn, why doesn't why why
Schultz don't just focus on uh um
Flagrant 2, which was doing massive
numbers more than um focus on um
Brilliant Idiots. And no, he's forever
indebted to to to Charlemagne, right?
Like I I do believe that Charlemagne has
people indebted to him and I think Jay-Z
as well. By the way, there's nothing
wrong with what I'm saying that I
believe these people do. I think that's
dope because eventually I want I got to
start doing that too. You know what I
mean? Um for the full take over the over
the industry, but we got to do it an
independent way. That the way I'm
realizing is that
everybody that's that you would consider
if you could consider I have a posy.
Yeah. There maybe were inspired by me,
but we all just have YouTube channels,
right? and and there's no like power
play to be done. Let me tell you what a
power play is. If one of the new media
guys, and I'm hoping, you know, [ __ ]
you know, I guess I've been in that
position at times. If one of the new
media guys became like
the head of music
or the head of music, hiphop at YouTube
or something. You get what I'm saying?
That's a power play, right? So, here's
the thing now. That person and and
that's how Jay-Z uses people, right?
Jay-Z when when you look at the
Rockefeller tree, he put them [ __ ] not
really because they they did their work,
too. But they all fell in powerful
positions, right? So, you got this guy
over here, he's running that label. This
guy over here, he worked for this DSP.
This guy over here, he's the head
content guy at that media company. So
their power ba basically
exponentially um expands to eventually
when needed defend Jay-Z or Rock
Nation's interest if there ever is a
time that it needs defending. Do you get
what I'm saying? So it's the same thing
I was saying with Charlemagne.
Charlemagne utilized like you know like
he had u um car blanch um at
MTV when everything with Charlemagne was
a go. What he did was he took the bum
off the bodega which is with Taxone. Hey
get on the show. I think Tax Stone was
down to kill a [ __ ] for Charlemagne. I
think Charlemagne knew that [ __ ] was a
crash out honestly. I promise y I think
Charlemagne only [ __ ] with him just to
be like all right bro. One day I might
need you to clap a [ __ ] for me. stupid
ass [ __ ] just clapped the wrong [ __ ] I
guess. I don't know. Rest in peace Bum.
Um but yeah, and then I think
Charlemagne helps out the Angela because
respectfully I I don't be trying to
listen to these [ __ ] bro. Like
I used to be watching Brilliant Idiots
from watching like Breakfast Club and
I'm like, "Yo, another Angela Ry
interview, bro. Like, yo, what are we
doing, bro?" Like, I'll be watching the
I'm watching the Breakfast Club. I look
at my notification. I'm like, bro,
another But I can't knock it. He's
putting on his squad. He puts on his
squad. They get they get like a
correspondent role at CNN or MSNBC
that might turn to some other [ __ ]
Later on, they put out a book together.
I think, you know, it's power plays. You
know, I always talk to Charlamine and
Charlemagne always say this, you know,
when the complex puts out the list and
the list is powerful. I don't what is
it? Best media. I was two this year or
whatever. Was that two? I can't remember
what that was. Anyway, when they put
Wait, no, it was one. Wait, was I one
this year? I don't even know
the last media list. What What number
was I chat? No, I was two, right? Yeah,
I was two. I was two. I was two. Okay.
Okay. Okay. Yeah.
Okay. When they put out these lists and
I spoke to Char about this bunch. He's
like, "Yo, act." He usually sends me a
different list and he's like, "Yo, act,
this is what true power is." And I think
on face value, some people might take
that as hate. But that's not hate. He's
not hating on the list. He's always on
the list. Like not like top three, but
he's on the list. But when he's talking
about power, he's talking about, yo, I
could go get this person a show or I
could walk this person into [ __ ] CNN
and have like that is power. And I think
that's important. So anyway, that's why
I was talking about the posies and [ __ ]
like that. Like those are the real when
you when you when you start get higher
up in the in the game, you start realize
a lot of these powerful dudes, they get
a posi, but they use their power and
influence in putting people wherever
they need to be done or be put. that's
their influence. Anyway, I'm kind of
getting long-winded here. Um, but I said
that to say Amanda Seals, I always felt
like she was one of them. Wasn't she on
Guy Code?
I felt like her and Charlemagne. I felt
like Charlemagne kind of like I was
never trying to ever see her. No
disrespect. Charlemagne would give her
visibility, which I would usually think
that's the posi move that you would then
later
defend him in case it's he ever needs to
be defended on some Jay-Z [ __ ] You know
what I mean? But I see shorty
deflecting. So, I'm now wondering what
the [ __ ] happened.
But
from what I understand, what you're
saying is like, do I feel like I did?
Yes and no.
you know, like I I mean I I went to the
industry to
achieve
a certain level of
acknowledgement. Same Ada, the feeling
is mutual.
Um
>> Okay, come on now.
>> And I do feel like I did that. However,
I think it was only to a certain extent
because
um
because basically once I
Why would I do a podcast with
Charlamagne? Why Why would I do a
podcast with Charlemagne? We had great
chemistry until I realized that he was a
ridiculous person and he was a snake. So
then we don't have great chemistry
anymore. He's also not an intellectual.
Like he's read books. He's not a dummy,
but he's not intellectual and he's not
he don't got no backbone. He sits here
and he regurgitates the same crap and
the people that he does challenge, like
remember when he challenged Kla Harris,
remember when she was on his show and he
was like, "So, who's actually in charge
of the Democrats, you know, uh Joe Biden
or Joe Mansion, and she blackwomaned him
and started saying like, "NO, ABSOLUTELY
NOT." She didn't he didn't even come
back because he didn't have no he didn't
have no way to come back at her because
he didn't know anything further than
what he said. And
>> yo, Charlemagne,
this is a perfect time to tap this. This
is where you tap in your Luca. Angela
Ry, this is where you get on. This is
this is your this is your job to
dismantle this right here.
>> Then they have people on the show and
they allow them to just talk they and to
talk their [ __ ] and they don't have the
actual knowledge and the actual
intellectualism
and or the actual backbone to be able to
check them and reveal the nonsense that
they're spewing. And whether that's
Larry Elder or that other broad or um
the guy from the ADL,
etc.
>> Now, Larry Elder did drop 70 points on
him. I can't cap with you, but I think
Larry Elder will drop 70 on her, too.
And even matter of fact, I I I think um
I think I think they brought in um
Angela Ry for um Larry Elder. Wait, was
it?
And he's still giving the [ __ ] beats.
Hold on.
>> Anyway, go look up that Larry Elder
interview at Breakfast Club.
>> Like, sit to rappers.
>> Now, I'm gonna be honest with you.
I I have been really impressed by
Charlemagne's depth. Pause. Whoa, that
sounded crazy. I've been impressed by
his depth in I I I think he's gotten
really really better at
political commentary. Now, at first I
was skeptical and I was going to I
thought it was going to be outside of
his his um his realm. Here's why. I know
Charlemagne is not a stupid [ __ ] but I
know Charlemagne plays a stupid [ __ ] on
Breakfast Club. And no disrespect. What?
What I mean by that? Like the lowhanging
like Charmand is still acting like he
can't pronounce words. Like come on,
bro. Like you're 40. Come on. I love
Charmand by the way. This is no this,
right? But but like
that's for comedic relief. That's for
entertainment. When I talked to Char, I
was like, he's a very intellectual,
smart guy. Like, you know what I mean?
Charam be like, "Yo, what that word
mean?" Like, you know what I mean? But
that was that was part of a stickick,
right? Like that was like it's kind of
like stiffen seats. Charlemagne is
highly educated, right? Charlemagne is a
writer. He's an author. He reads a lot
as well. He learns.
At first, I thought to be I thought he
wouldn't farewell in politics or
political commentary if he didn't shed
this like, you know, almost willfully
stupid, you know, stickick that
sometimes he utilizes on the Breakfast
Club to get jokes because people don't
like hearing ideas about intricate
subjects from people they don't feel are
feel um
are smart. And
that's when I realized I'm like, "No,
no, he knows how to either balance it or
he clearly could erase that stick where
people don't think of him as, yo, why am
I listening to Charlemagne?" You know
what I mean? I actually listen to
Charlemagne for political commentary.
And I think a lot of times I've been,
you know, I don't I don't know,
obviously I don't get too much into
politics here because I just think it's
too divisive. And um everybody know I
[ __ ] voted for Trump. So like I don't
want y'all to be like I'm trying to push
Trump on you. So I don't even try to
talk politics too much. But
I listen to Charlemagne's like, you
know, political commentary these days
and, you know, within the realm that I'm
comfortable with knowing about it, he'd
be spot on. Charlemagne know his [ __ ]
Which I didn't think he would be that
type of person. So I gotta give him his
credit for that. So I I actually, you
know, I'm going against what Man of Seal
says. I don't think Charlemagne is
stupid or I don't think Charlemagne is
um you know should stick to rappers. I
think honestly honestly I think
Charlemagne is one of the most important
black voices when it comes to politics.
This is going to sound crazy. I think
Stephen A. Smith is too. Stephen A.
Smith is a couple levels above, but
we're getting to realize some of the
loudest voices aren't political voices.
And you know what it is? I think people
want to hear political commentary from
people who aren't political analysts
just sitting there kind of regurgitating
talking points. Not saying that he's not
regurgitating talking points at some
point, but at least he speaks in
layman's terms. He'll speak as if he is
you and not speak as if he's just a
programmed drone robot. And um that does
matter. The way how you communicate even
the same regurgitated talking points
does matter.
>> Yes, Andrew Schultz can say whatever and
then he depends him. So, you know, go
for it, playboy.
>> I love Andrew Schultz,
>> but that's not my peoples no more.
>> Wait, is he like downing? He's downing
um Charlemagne over Andrew Schultz.
What?
Everybody been know that he's been doing
a show with Andrew Schultz. What's the
problem?
>> I don't do Christmas anymore. So, my mom
doesn't do Christmas anymore.
>> Okay. Anyway,
Charlemagne, man,
you got to put one of your pit bulls on
the team to to to uh you know, put this
fire out right here. But, uh, Amanda
Seals, yo, she she seems like every time
I see her online, she's always
complaining. Like, it's like, wo is me.
Somebody did me wrong. Somebody's not
doing whatever. Like, I've never seen
her say, "Hey, listen. I'm very
confident. I'm happy. I'm I'm I'm I'm
fighting for so and so, but I'm not
grumpy. Like the person who always got
something to say about somebody else, at
some point you start saying maybe the
problem is you, right? So, I'm getting
like that common denominator syndrome
with her where it's like, "Hey, listen.
If you're kind of coming with gripes
about people consistently, maybe we got
to start looking at you, right?" All
right.